(Penny:)And even if Raj wanted
something, he couldn't tell me.
(Penny:)Howard won't order anything,
(Penny:)but he will come up
with some sort of skeevy comment
(Penny:)involving the words pie
or cheesecake.
(Penny:)And Leonard's
lactose intolerant,
(Penny:)so he can't eat anything here
(Penny:)without his intestines
blowing up
(Penny:)like a balloon animal.
(Leonard:)Hang on a second.
(Leonard:)I could have the fruit platter.
(Penny:)You want the fruit platter?
(Leonard:)Does it have melon
on it?
Yeah.
(Leonard:)No, I can't eat melon.
(Penny:)Oh, Howard,
heads up.
(Penny:)Your ex-girlfriend just
came in for her shift.
(Leonard:)When was the last time
you saw her?
(Howard:)Oh, not since we broke up.
(Howard:)Wow. How am I going
to play this?
(Howard:)Sophisticated and relaxed?
(Howard:)Friendly, noncommittal?
(Howard:)Cold and distant?
(Bernadette:)Hi, guys.
Hey.
(Sheldon:)Hello.
(Sheldon:)I see you decided to go
with pathetic and frightened.
(Raj:)It's one of his best moves.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪